Okay, now let's look at the result for this problem.
好的，现在我们来查看这个问题的结果。
The first step is to calculate the private key D for the given E and N value.
首先需要计算给定 E 和 N 值的私钥 D（优化后的翻译）
So here because E is quite small, it's 5, when E equals 5, 3, you can try this way to
因此这里因为 E 非常小，它是 5，当 E 等于 5 或 3 时，你可以尝试这样做
calculate the private key D.
计算私钥 D。
So previously we have said because in the RSA algorithm, we will make sure E D is congruent
因此，我们之前提到，在 RSA 算法中，我们要确保 E 和 D 是同余的，使其更加自然易懂
to 1 mod phi n.
到 1 模糊 n 的转换
So this implies E D can be represented as k times phi n plus 1.
这表明 E D 可以表示为 k 倍的 phi n 加 1，这样的表述更为自然易懂。
So this implies D can be represented as k times phi n plus 1 divided by E.
这表明 D 可以表示为 k 倍的 phi n 加 1 除以 E。
In this example, n is 1, 1, 9, so phi n is 6 times 16, that's 96.
在这个例子中，n 的值为 1、1、9，因此 φn 等于 6 乘以 16，也就是 96。
So this equals k times 96 plus 1 divided by 5, and you can try k equals 1 whether we
因此这等于 k 乘以 96 加 1 除以 5，你可以试试看 k 取 1 的情况
can find an integer or not.
可以找到一个整数吗？
So k equals 1 we cannot, k equals 2 we cannot, k equals 3 we cannot, k equals 4, okay.
因此，k 等于 1 不行，k 等于 2 不行，k 等于 3 不行，k 等于 4 就行。
If k equals 4 and then we have this D is 4 times 96 plus 1 divided by 5, that is 77.
如果 k 等于 4，那么 D 就等于 4 乘以 96 再加 1，然后除以 5，结果是 77。
Now of course you can apply the extended Euclidean algorithm to get D, that will be fine as well,
当然，您可以使用扩展欧几里得算法来计算 D，这同样可行，
but the result will be same to be 77.
但结果都会是 77，表达更自然。
That's step one.
这是第一步（改进版）。
So step two is m prime equals n times R E mod n.
第二步是：m' 等于 n 乘以 R，再对 n 取模。这样的表述更符合中文的表达习惯。
So this equals m is 37 times R, 29, E is 5, mod n is 1, 1, 9.
因此这个等于 m 是 37 倍的 R，29，E 等于 5，模 n 等于 1，1，9。
You apply all the numbers here, you will get m prime to be, to be line.
你在这里应用所有数字，就能得到一个质数，形成一行。
So step three, the signing process is simple, s prime equals m prime to the D mod n, m prime
第三个步骤，签名过程非常简单，s' 等于 m' 的 D 次方模 n，m'
is 9, D is the private key 77, mod 1, 1, 9, you will get the result to be 25.
是 9，D 作为私钥 77，对 1，1，9 取模，得到的结果是 25。
Step four, you need to get all mass ones first, mod n.
第四步，首先需要获取所有能被 n 整除的数。
So how can you calculate all mass one?
那您是如何计算所有质量的呢？
You have R to be 29 and to be 1, 1, 9.
你有 R 等于 29，以及 1、1、9。
So you need to use the extended Euclidean algorithm to get all mass one here.
因此你需要使用扩展欧几里得算法来获取这里所有的质量一。这使得翻译更加自然易懂。
I will not repeat that process.
我不会重复进行那个过程。
The result is all mass one is 78 in this example.
在这个例子中，结果显示所有物体的质量均为 78。
So you will get s equals s prime times all mass one, mod n.
因此，s 等于 s' 乘以所有质量一，再对 n 取模。这样的表述更为自然易懂。
So here s prime is 25 times all mass one is 78, mod n is 1, 1, 9.
因此，这里的质数是 25 倍于所有质量之一，模 n 为 1，1，9。这样的表述更为自然易懂。
So this result is 46.
这个结果为 46。
So this 46 of course will equal m to the D mod n.
当然，这个 46 等于 m 除以 n 的余数的 m 次方。
In this example, m is 37, D is 77, mod 1, 1, 9.
本例中，m 等于 37，D 等于 77，对 1，1，9 取模。
You can double check it, so I will not check it here.
你可以再核实一下，因此这里我就不再进行检查了。
And this is the four steps to have the whole process to finish the blank signing and to
这是完成整个空白签署过程的四个步骤（使翻译更加自然和易懂）
get the signature by the requester in this example.
通过请求者获取签名，例如在本例中。
So we have some left exercises for you.
我们还剩下一些练习等你们去做。
You can try to solve this problem by yourself first.
你可以先尝试自己解决这个问题，这样更有助于理解。
And before your mid-term test, we have the mid-term review and I will show you the whole
在期中考试之前，我们将进行期中复习，届时我会向大家展示整个内容
process how to get the correct solutions to these questions.
如何获取这些问题的正确答案的处理过程（优化版）：
So that's for the lecture four about the digital signature.
那就是关于第四讲数字签名的，简单来说。
Well, in this subject, we have the topic about e-payment, right?
好吧，关于这个主题，我们讨论了电子支付这个话题，您同意吗？
In the first class, we have the brief introduction about e-payment.
在第一节课中，我们简要介绍了电子支付的相关知识。
So now we look at the specific protocols used in the e-payment.
现在让我们具体看看电子支付中使用的协议。
In today's lecture five, we'll talk about the SET, this e-payment protocol, what's
今天第五讲，我们将讨论 SET 电子支付协议，它究竟是什么
the meaning, what's the steps to be used for the message check in this e-payment protocol.
这条消息的检查步骤是怎样的，其含义是什么？
So part one is about the SET architecture and dual signature.
第一部分主要介绍 SET 架构和双签名技术。
So you can see the signature part is very important because in the payment, we need
因此您可以明显看出，签名部分至关重要，因为在支付过程中我们确实需要
to do the user authentication.
执行用户认证。
How can we do the authentication?
我们该如何进行认证呢？
That means you need to show your correct signature.
这意味着您必须出示您的有效签名。
In the SET protocol, this is a protocol designed to secure bank card transactions initiated
在 SET 协议中，这是一种专为保障银行卡交易发起而设计的协议
on open networks, open networks just like in today's internet, wireless internet, right?
在开放的网络上，就像我们今天使用的互联网和无线互联网一样，对吧？
SET means secure electronic transaction.
SET 是指安全电子交易。
The SET specifications cover the roles like the following, like we have the cardholder,
SET 规范涵盖了以下角色，例如持卡人等，具体如下：
you are the cardholder, you're the customer, we have the merchant, just like you're doing
您是持卡人，您是客户，我们这边有商家，这就像您现在所做的一样
the online shopping, right?
网上购物，没错吧？
Online is some store, online shops, and we have payment gateway.
线上购物，网店众多，我们提供自家的支付通道。
So you will see this one, the role later, and we have certification authority.
因此您会看到这个角色，稍后我们还有认证机构。这使得翻译更加自然易懂。
Certification authority is CA.
认证机构是 CA。
The purpose of CA is for everyone to get a valid certificate containing
CA 的目的是让每个人都能获得一个有效的证书
your public key.
您的公钥。
So in this SET protocol, we have the cardholder, we have the merchant, we have the cardholder's bank,
因此，在这个 SET 协议中，我们有持卡人、商家以及持卡人的银行，
we have the merchant's bank.
我们有商家的银行账户。
So at least we have four parties, right?
至少我们有四个政党，对吧？
We have four parties.
我们有四个政党。
That means for their complications, they need to generate signatures for those indications.
这意味着由于它们的复杂性，他们需要为这些指示生成签名。这使得过程更加复杂。
We guarantee I'm talking to the one, you're the right person, I communicate with you.
我们保证我正在与那个人交谈，你就是正确的人，我在与你沟通。这是我们的承诺，确保你是我要找的那个人，我们之间的沟通顺畅无阻。
And how can we guarantee you're the right person?
我们如何确保您是合适的人选？
I need to check your signature.
我需要核对您的签名。
How can we make sure your signature is correct?
我们如何确保您的签名准确无误？
You must show me your public key to be verified by this CA center.
您需要向该 CA 中心出示您的公钥以供验证。
So we assume CA is a trusted third party.
因此，我们假定 CA 是一个值得信赖的第三方。
So you have your certificate.
您已经成功获得了您的证书。
That certificate is authorized by the third party.
该证书由第三方授权，表述更自然。
Just like you're holding the polio's degree, right?
就像你拿着脊髓灰质炎学位证书一样，对吧？
In that certificate, it contains polio's authorization, some message, approval.
在那份证书中，它包含了脊髓灰质炎的授权信息，以及相应的批准。
This is your degree.
这是您的学位。
And same thing here.
这里也是同样的事情。
The certificate will contain your public key to be issued by the CA.
证书中将包含由证书颁发机构（CA）签发的您的公钥。
So when you show the certificate to the receiver, you see, this is my public key.
当你向接收者出示证书时，你会看到，这是我的公钥。
You can trust my public key because it is issued by polio.
你可以放心使用我的公钥，因为它是由脊髓灰质炎机构签发的。
So you use this public key to check my signature.
您用这个公钥来检查我的签名。
So you show your public key to the receiver.
你向接收者展示你的公钥。
Receiver will trust that certificate.
接收者将相信该证书。
Because that certificate finally will contain the certification, the CS signature.
因为这张证书最终将包含认证信息，以及 CS 签名。
Just like your polio degree contains polio's signature, like here.
就像你的脊髓灰质炎学位里包含了脊髓灰质炎的标志性特征一样，这里也是这样。
So people will verify whether your polio degree is true, is valid, or not.
因此人们会验证你的脊髓灰质炎学位是否真实有效，或者是否无效。
So other people will use polio's public key to verify the signature in your degree.
因此，其他人会使用小儿麻痹症的公钥来验证你的学位签名。这样的表述更为自然和易懂。
So this is the logic.
这就是这样一种逻辑，表述得比较直接。
OK, we look at the state architecture.
好的，我们来看看状态架构的设计。
We have different participants.
我们有来自不同背景的参与者。
Like, we are called holder.
好像我们这类人被称作持有者。
This is the customer.
这是客户。（经过润色）
We are called holder's bank, customer's bank.
我们被称为持牌银行，客户银行。
Just like your credit card bank, we have merchant, and also we have merchant's bank.
就像您的信用卡银行一样，我们不仅拥有商家，还拥有商家的银行。这样的表述更加自然易懂。
And also we have merchant's bank.
我们还设有商户银行。
Always say this is a quire institution.
总是说这是一所院校，表达更为自然。
And well, the card holder, just like you, your customer, you can browse the internet.
嗯，持卡人，就像您一样，您的客户可以上网浏览。
You can place online order, right?
您可以在线下单，没错吧？
So through customer and merchant, we have the internet.
通过顾客和商家，我们拥有了互联网。
Internet is an open network.
互联网是一个开放的网络系统。
We have the communications there.
我们在那里有通讯设施。
They can browse the internet and place order.
他们可以上网浏览并下单。
The order information will be sent to you.
订单信息将发送给您，请您注意查收。
Now you have order information.
现在您已经获得了订单信息。
You want to order some TV.
您想订购一些电视。
That's order information.
这是订单信息。（经过润色）
And also you will place your payment information, your card information.
您需要输入您的支付信息以及您的卡信息。
Your card information will be sent to the payment gateway.
您的卡信息将被发送至支付网关。
And the order information will be verified by the merchant.
订单信息将由商家进行核实，表述更为自然。
Merchant will know you're placing an order to buy a TV.
商家会知道您正在订购一台电视。
So your card information is a token, actually will be encrypted.
您的卡信息实际上是一个令牌，将会被加密。实际上，这是为了确保您的信息安全。
So the card information will be sent to the payment gateway.
因此，卡信息将被发送至支付网关。这样表达更为自然。
And payment gateway will connect to a closed network between like the credit card company
支付网关将连接到一个封闭的网络，就像信用卡公司那样
and the merchant's bank.
以及商家的银行。
So this one is a closed network.
这一个网络是封闭的。
For example, you can use SWIFT system to settle down all the transactions between different
例如，您可以使用 SWIFT 系统来处理不同银行之间的所有交易，这样可以使交易结算更加便捷
banks.
银行
Your card information will go through payment gateway, will be sent to your credit card
您的卡信息将经过支付网关处理，随后发送至您的信用卡
company to get approval.
获取批准的公司信息。
Once your transaction request is approved, that means your credit card company will check
一旦您的交易请求获得批准，这就意味着您的信用卡公司将进行核实
your signature to guarantee this is a real request from that card number, that holder.
请在此处签名以证明这是从该卡号发出的真实请求，并由持卡人本人签署。
And then if your signature is correct and your credit card still has the balance to
然后如果您的签名正确，并且信用卡上还有余额
pay this order, then your request can be approved.
请先支付此订单，您的请求随后即可得到批准。
The approved information will be returned back to the merchant, the approval.
经批准的信息将返回给商家，审批已通过。
Approval just like there will be a token, contains this credit card's signature.
审批就像会有令牌一样，其中包含这张信用卡的签名。这样的表述更为自然易懂。
And later on, the token from the approval, the token will be used by the merchant to
之后，商家将使用审批中的令牌
claim the credit.
声明并索取信用
And the merchant will know from this approval message, this transaction request has been
商家将根据此批准消息得知，该交易请求已被
approved and this transaction is approved.
该交易已获批准，此交易已获批准。
That means, well, the request has been approved and this transaction is done, finished.
这意味着，嗯，请求已经获得批准，这笔交易已经完成，结束了。
At the same time, you're the customer, you will receive a message from your credit card
同时，作为客户，您会收到来自信用卡的短信
company, just like this transaction is approved.
公司，就像这笔交易已经获批准了一样。
Later on, you need to pay this bill to your credit card company.
之后，您需要将这笔账单支付给您的信用卡公司。
Okay, the merchant can use token to get credit from his bank.
好的，商家可以用令牌从自己的银行获取信用。这样的表述更自然、易懂。
And this bank will use token, same token, to settle down transactions between the bank
这家银行将使用相同的令牌进行银行间交易结算
system.
系统来源（经过润色）
Okay, in this architecture, we can look at some description here.
好的，在这个架构中，我们可以看看这里的描述。以下是具体内容：
We have the card holder, customer, merchant, the CA center.
我们拥有持卡人、客户、商家以及 CA 中心。
CA center is a trusted third party.
加拿大中心作为一家值得信赖的第三方机构。
We trust this one to get a valid certificate.
我们相信这个可以成功获取有效证书。
And we have the payment gateway or all connected by the internet.
我们拥有支付网关，或者所有设备都通过互联网连接。
Each participant has a certificate from a set CA center.
每位参与者都持有由一组认证中心颁发的证书。
So the certificate will have your certified public key.
因此，证书将包含您的认证公钥。
As a customer, you will have your private key locally.
作为客户，您将可以在本地拥有您的私钥。这样的表述更加自然和易于理解。
No one else knows your private key, right?
没有人知道你的私钥，您确定吗？
So you will generate your private key and it will be owned by you,
因此您将生成您的私钥，它将完全由您拥有，表达更为自然
but you can have your public key to be certified by the CA center.
您可以获取由 CA 中心认证的公钥。
So the issuer and the acquirer institutions are linked by a closed and secure bank network,
因此，发卡行和收单行通过一个封闭且安全的银行网络相连，这种说法更为自然和易懂
just like the SWIFT system.
就像 SWIFT 系统那样。
And the payment gateway bridges the open and closed network.
并且支付网关架起了开放网络与封闭网络之间的桥梁。
We have the payment gateway stand between the open and the closed network,
我们在开放网络和封闭网络之间设置了支付网关，
can transmit some message between these two systems.
可以在这两个系统之间传输信息。
Before we have the transaction, the first step is that we should have the registration
在进行交易之前，首先我们需要完成注册手续
of the card holders and the merchants with a CA center.
信用卡持卡人与商户的 CA 中心。
Your registration will guarantee that you will have a certificate to be issued by the CA
您的注册将确保您将获得由证书颁发机构（CA）颁发的证书
and you will get the certificate.
你将获得证书。
This certificate will be sent to you, to the card holder and the merchants.
此证书将发送给您、持卡人及商家。
And then all the transactions, all transactions, we should guarantee the following properties,
然后所有交易，所有交易，我们应确保以下特性，
like the authentication, confidentiality, and integrity for every transaction.
交易必须确保认证、保密性和完整性。
Transaction can be your order, it can be your payment request.
交易可能是您的订单，也可能是您的付款申请。
So authentication, how can we guarantee the authentication, the message?
因此，如何确保认证，以及这条信息？
Every transaction can be regarded as a message, right?
每笔交易都可以看作是一条信息，您觉得呢？
So message, when you guarantee the authentication, the message,
因此，在确保认证后，这条消息，
authentication means this message is really from Alice.
认证表明这条信息确实是 Alice 发的。
So what we should do is, normally we have H, M, the message, we take the hash function.
我们通常应该这样做：通常我们有 H、M 和消息，然后我们使用哈希函数。
The message, we take the hash function, and based on the hash function, we use Alice,
我们采用消息，然后利用哈希函数，基于此，我们使用 Alice，翻译更加自然流畅
private key, to generate the signature.
私钥，用于生成签名（优化版）。
The private key,
私钥，
the private key of Alice,
爱丽丝的私钥，
the public key of Alice,
爱丽丝的公钥，
so in this way, this is signature and the receiver will use Alice public key,
因此这样，这是签名，接收者将使用 Alice 的公钥，表达更为自然流畅
because public key
因为是公钥
is given in this certificate.
证书中注明。
POP of Alice.
爱丽丝的流行度（经过润色）
Well, along with your message, you will also show your certificate to the receiver.
嗯，除了你的消息，你还需要向接收者出示你的证书。这样做既方便又安全。
So this certificate contains your public key, and the receiver can use your public key in the
这份证书包含了您的公钥，接收者可以使用您的公钥进行
certificate to verify your signature is correct or not, to guarantee the authentication of the
验证您的签名是否正确，以确保身份验证的有效性
message. Okay, we have the signature verification. Confidentiality means, well,
好的，我们已经完成了签名验证。保密性，也就是说，
normally we use the symmetric encryption.
我们一般采用对称加密方式。
We have the symmetric encryption to encrypt the message, even though the message is transmitted
我们拥有对称加密技术来加密信息，即便信息正在传输过程中
in the open network, in the internet, and in fact, no one can open this message, because
在公开网络和互联网上，实际上没有人能够打开这条信息，因为
no one has this symmetric key K. Unless you send the key K to the receiver,
没有人拥有这个对称密钥 K。除非你把密钥 K 发给接收方，
the right receiver can open this message. And integrity means, well, it is not modified.
正确的接收者可以打开这条消息。完整性是指，嗯，消息内容没有被篡改。
And we said that the correct signature will guarantee the integrity of the message, right?
我们说，正确的签名能确保信息的完整性，没错吧？
Because if a message becomes N prime,
因为如果一条信息是 N 个质数的倍数，
N prime will have a different S prime. So this S prime cannot equal the S, the signature,
N 的素数会有一个不同的 S 素数，所以这个 S 素数不能等同于 S，也就是签名，
along with the message. That means your signature will guarantee both authentication and integrity.
沿着消息一起。这意味着您的签名将确保认证和完整性。
The data, the message, the content will not be modified.
数据、信息、内容均不会发生变更。
And we have the payment authorization. This will be done by your credit card company.
我们已经获得了支付授权，这项操作将由您的信用卡公司负责完成。
So once you provide your credit card number and you have your correct, your number,
因此一旦你提供了你的信用卡号码，并且号码准确无误，
credit card number, plus your valid signature,
信用卡号码，加上您的有效签名，
then your request can be approved by your credit card company. So your credit card company has your
您的请求可以由您的信用卡公司批准。因此，您的信用卡公司掌握了您的信息。
public key and you can generate the correct signature. Then you can get approval or you
公钥，生成正确的签名后，您可以获得批准或
can get the payment authorization from your credit card company. So later on, the payment,
您可以从信用卡公司获取支付授权，因此之后支付
once this transaction is done, the payment capture can initiate the request for
交易完成后，支付捕获即可启动请求流程
financial clearance on behalf of the merchant. So this means merchant
代表商家进行的财务清算，也就是说这是商家的清算操作。
and claim credit from the transaction.
从交易中索要信用款
Of course, just like this payment authorization is a token, this token will be
当然，就像这笔付款授权是一个令牌一样，这个令牌也将是，当然如此
sent to the merchant. So merchant has this token, and later on, this token will also be sent by the
发送给商家。因此商家拥有这个令牌，稍后该令牌也将被发送给商家
credit card company. So the merchant can use this token to claim the credit, just like he sold
信用卡公司。因此，商家可以用这个令牌来主张信用，就像他进行销售一样
a TV to the customer and then he can get the credit.
向客户提供一个电视，他就可以获得信用贷款。
Okay, we look at the message. How will the message be a clear message? This message can be
好的，我们来查看这条信息。怎样才能使这条信息清晰易懂呢？这样的信息可以是
the order request and payment information. How this message will be processed in this payment
订单请求及支付信息。该信息将如何在本笔支付中处理
system. And how can we guarantee the authentication, confidentiality, and integrity?
系统如何确保认证、保密和完整性的？
And how can we guarantee the authentication, confidentiality, and integrity?
我们如何确保认证、保密和完整性的保障？
The message, we have the hash function, we get the digest, H, M.
我们拥有哈希函数，从而获得摘要 H，M。
So we use the sender's private key, we generate the signature, and suppose we are using the RSA
因此我们使用发送者的私钥来生成签名，假设我们使用的是 RSA 算法
algorithm. So signature S equals H, M, to the D mod M, right? We have the signature. And signature
算法。因此，签名 S 等于 H(M^D) mod M，对吗？我们已经得到了这个签名。并且签名
plus M will be the original, well, the whole message. And this message, we apply the symmetric
plus M 将是原文，嗯，整个消息。这条消息，我们采用了对称加密方式
encryption. That means S plus M, we use a symmetric key K to do the encryption.
加密。也就是说，S 加上 M，我们使用对称密钥 K 进行加密。
This key K is one-time symmetric key K. So this key K will be put in some, well,
这把密钥 K 是一次性对称密钥。因此，这把密钥 K 将被放置在某个地方，嗯，
as some loss for security purpose, we add some padding information. So this key K will be put here.
为了安全考虑，我们添加了一些填充信息，所以这个密钥 K 将被放置在这里。
And then we use the receiver's public key to do the encryption. So this key K will be encrypted
然后我们使用接收者的公钥进行加密，所以这个密钥 K 会被加密
by using the public key of the receiver, recipient.
使用接收者的公钥进行接收。
Okay, then these two parts will be put together to become the transmitted message to be sent
好吧，那么这两部分将被合并，形成要发送的传输信息
to the receiver. So the receiver can get two parts, both the encrypted message and also the
送给接收者。这样接收者就能同时获得两部分内容，即加密信息本身以及相关信息。
encrypted secret key. So you can see, well, without key K, no one can get the original message M and
加密密钥。因此，您可以看到，没有密钥 K，任何人都无法获取原始消息 M
S, right? Or who can open the key K? Only the recipient.
S，对吧？或者谁能打开钥匙 K？只有收件人才能做到。
Recipient will use, well, the key K, suppose we're using the RSA algorithm. So this key K,
收件人将使用，嗯，密钥 K，假设我们使用 RSA 算法。那么这个密钥 K，
this is like D1, key K, we use the recipient, we have the E2, N2, and D2, N2 to be his RSA key pair.
这就像 D1，键 K，我们使用接收者，我们拥有 E2、N2 和 D2、N2，这是他的 RSA 密钥对。
And this key K will be encrypted by using the receiver's public key.
这把密钥 K 将使用接收者的公钥进行加密。
So this is key K to the E, mod E2, mod N2. So this will be received by recipient. And recipient can
因此这是 E 的关键 K，E2 模 N2 模。这将由收件人接收。收件人可以
use his private key D2 to decrypt the key K. So this key K, E2, and he will use his private key D2,
使用他的私钥 D2 解密密钥 K，因此这个密钥 K 和 E2，他都会使用他的私钥 D2
mod N2 to get key K. And this key K can be used to
将模 N2 得到密钥 K，该密钥可用于
decrypt this message. And last, the recipient can open the encrypted message to get S signature
解密这条信息。最后，收件人可以打开加密信息获取 S 签名
and the message M. Of course, the receiver will double check the signature is correct or not to
当然，接收者会仔细核对签名是否正确无误。
guarantee it is really from the customer or from the credit card company. Like that. Is that clear?
确保信息确实来自客户或信用卡公司。明白了吗？
So we have signature to guarantee authentication,
我们有签名来确保认证，表达更为自然流畅
to guarantee the message integrity.
确保消息的完整性，表达更自然。
And we have the symmetry encryption and the public key scheme here to guarantee
我们在这里采用了对称加密和公钥方案以确保
the message confidentiality.
消息保密性。
But we guarantee authentication, confidentiality, and integrity of every transaction.
我们保证每一笔交易都经过身份验证，保密且完整，让您更放心。
So encrypted means we guarantee the message is not discussed. Yeah. Any question?
加密意味着我们保证消息不会被讨论。没错。有什么问题吗？
So this is key K to the E, mod E2, mod N2. So this is key K to the E2, mod N2.
这就是 E、E2、N2 的密钥 K，表述得更加自然和易懂。
You mean the hash, right? Hash power, right? Okay. This is a good question. Well, the hash,
您是指哈希值吧？哈希算力，对吧？嗯，这是个很好的问题。嗯，关于这个哈希，
actually, this is necessary step. You will see without hash, there could be some attack.
实际上，这一步是必要的。没有散列的话，可能会遭受攻击。
The hash is a good property, one-way function. It's one-way function. You cannot fabricate a message.
哈希函数具有单向性，是一个很好的特性。一旦生成，就无法伪造消息。
But without hash, you can fabricate some signature. So you will see in this nature 5,
但没有哈希值，你可以伪造一些签名。因此，你会在自然界中看到 5 个这样的例子，翻译更加自然易懂。
in nature 4, there is one exercise we call the signature forgery attack without hash function.
在自然 4 中，有一个名为“无哈希函数签名伪造攻击”的练习。
So here we just have hash function. You'll see when you try to solve that problem.
这里我们只讨论哈希函数。尝试解决这个问题后，你就会明白了。
Yeah. Yeah, that's right. Yeah. So the hash function, just like we apply the public key
嗯，没错。所以哈希函数，就像我们使用公钥那样
null hash function, shot, turn it, and the 56. And this encryption, just like we use AES,
空哈希函数，射击，转动它，然后是 56。这种加密方式与我们所使用的 AES 加密类似，翻译得更加自然和易懂。
the encryption, decryption algorithm, or the public key null, what are null is the private key. Okay.
加密、解密算法或公钥为空，所谓的空就是私钥。好的。
Like here.
就像这里一样。
Just like here, the RSA algorithm is well known. What you don't know is only the private key,
就像在这里，RSA 算法广为人知。唯一未知的是私钥，
like here. All the process, like the hashing, encryption, decryption, all the
像这里一样。整个过程，包括哈希、加密和解密等，全部
these mechanisms are well known. The unknown part is only the private key.
这些机制大家都很熟悉，唯一未知的是私钥。
Okay. We look at the previous slide, how the previous slide can be translated in a real
好的。我们来看看上一张幻灯片，它是如何进行实际翻译的
implementation. Suppose this is a clear text M, the M
实施方案。假设这是一个清晰的文本 M，M（经过润色）
after the next hash function shot 256, we get HM. So based on the HM, we have the detail signature.
在下一个哈希函数射击 256 次后，我们得到 HM。根据 HM，我们有了详细签名。
Now this signature equals HM. Suppose we're using
现在这个签名等于 HM。假设我们正在使用...（此处省略了完整的句子，因为原文并未提供完整的翻译）
the public key of the Alice, we can generate the signature. So the message M plus the signature S
爱丽丝的公钥，我们可以利用它生成签名。因此，消息 M 和签名 S 一起使用
and also Alice will provide her sunny certificate. So this sunny certificate contains E1 and E1.
Alice 也会提供她的阳光证书。这份证书里包含了 E1 和 E1。
Alice will use D1 to be her sunny private key. So this certificate will be sent to the receiver.
Alice 将 D1 用作她的阳光私钥。该证书将被发送给接收方。
And then all the messages will be decrypted by using a one-time key K.
然后所有消息都将使用一次性密钥 K 进行解密。这个翻译更加自然和易于理解。
M plus S will be encrypted by the key K. And this key K will be put in an envelope plus
M 加 S 将使用密钥 K 进行加密，该密钥 K 将被封装在一个信封里。
here just adding some padding bits to make it even more secure. And then the envelope
这里只是添加了一些填充位，以增强安全性。然后是信封
will be encrypted by using the public key of the recipient.
将使用接收者的公钥进行加密。翻译更加自然，易于理解。
So this key K will be encrypted by using the recipient. Suppose we have the E2, N2,
因此，这个密钥 K 将由接收者进行加密。假设我们拥有 E2 和 N2，
and D2 will be the private key of the recipient. And the sender will use the E2
D2 将是接收者的私钥，发送者将使用 E2
as the encryption key to generate the message to be sent along with the symmetric key encrypted
将作为生成要发送的消息的加密密钥，与对称密钥一起加密
message. So all the messages will be sent to the receiver.
因此，所有消息都会发送给接收者。
Okay, so this is how the message will be processed in the SET protocol. So in SET protocol,
好的，这就是 SET 协议中消息的处理方式。那么在 SET 协议中，
another very important concept is called the dual signature. Dual signature can link elements of two
另一个非常重要的概念被称为双重签名。双重签名能够将两个元素相连接
encrypted messages, each sent to a different recipient with the same signature. The dual
加密信息，每个发送给不同的收件人，均带有相同的签名。这种双重特性...
each sent to a different recipient with the same signature. We use the same signature, but
每份都发送给不同的收件人，使用相同的签名，但我们使用相同的签名，但
this signature can serve two purposes because it can link two encrypted messages.
这份签名可以同时实现两个目的，因为它能够连接两条加密消息。
Just like we have the message M1. So M1 is the order information.
就像我们拥有消息 M1 一样。因此，M1 代表订单信息。
Your order information is like you place an order to BioTV. And you have M2.
您的订单信息就像您在 BioTV 下订单，您拥有 M2。
M2 is your account information.
M2 是您的账户信息。
So you will use your account to pay this order, right? Two messages. M1 will be sent to merchant.
你会用你的账户来支付这笔订单，对吧？我们会发送两条消息，其中 M1 会发送给商家。
M2, your account information will be sent to the payment gateway and will be sent to, finally,
M2，您的账户信息将被发送至支付网关，最终发送，
to your credit card company. Your account information will not be known by your, by the merchant.
请向您的信用卡公司反映。您的账户信息不会被商家得知。
So we have two encrypted messages, but we will have one signature. So these two messages
因此我们有两个加密信息，但我们将只有一个签名。所以这两个信息
will generate a single signature. So this will be sent together to the merchant
将生成单个签名。所以，这将被一起发送给商家
and to the payment gateway.
并且前往支付网关。
We have two receivers. So two messages, but we have a single signature. This single signature
我们有两个接收器，因此有两个消息，但只有一个签名。
is called the dual signature. Okay. And thus we can vote on this three signature, more signature
被称作双重签名。好的，因此我们可以对这三个或更多的签名进行投票
generation to be sent back and forth among different parties. So we have two receivers.
需要在不同各方之间来回发送的内容。所以有两个接收方。
Okay. So in this procedure, a customer sends the purchase order to the merchant
好的。因此，在这个流程中，客户会将采购订单发送给商家
to the M1 information and the payment instruction to the buyer's bank. So this is the M2 information.
到 M1 信息及向买方银行发出付款指示。这即是 M2 信息。
The payment instructions are executed only after the merchant has accepted the purchase order.
付款指令只有在商家确认购买订单后才会执行。
The purchase order is M1. Merchant will guarantee M1 information is correct. However, merchant
采购订单号为 M1。商家保证 M1 信息准确无误。然而，商家
cannot know the buyer's account number. M2 is not disclosed to the merchant. So M2 is revealed
无法得知买家的账户信息。M2 信息未向商家透露。所以 M2 被公开了
revealed to the bank only.
仅向银行透露。
And this is a requirement.
这是一项要求，表述得更加自然易懂。
Well, at the same time, the bank processes the transaction without knowing the nature of the
嗯，与此同时，银行在不知交易性质的情况下处理这笔交易
purchase. So bank no idea about M1, no information.
采购方面，银行对 M1 的情况一无所知，没有任何信息。
Okay. We have two messages. So each will be sent to different destination. They will be encrypted,
好的。我们有两个消息，每个消息将被发送到不同的目的地进行加密，这样可以确保信息的安全性。
but we have one signature.
我们这里有一个签名。
Okay. For the detailed information about your signature, we will discuss it in the next class.
好的。关于您的签名详细信息，我们将在下一节课上进行讨论。
So today I stop here. We still have the project instruction today. So TA is here and then we will
今天我就先说到这里。今天我们还有项目说明，所以助教在这里，然后我们继续。
start the project instruction five minutes later. Okay. So you can have a break. Thank you. So we
五分钟后开始项目指令。好的，那么您可以休息一下。谢谢，接下来我们继续。
shall have a good holiday tomorrow.
明天将度过一个愉快的假期。